<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wrydeas</title>
    <link>wry-wsac.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on wrydeas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:31:34 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="wry-wsac.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Caches, States, and Stores Oh My</title>
      <link>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/caches-states-and-stores-oh-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 14:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/caches-states-and-stores-oh-my/</guid>
      <description>In a recent discussion with coworkers we kept having to clarify the difference between a cache, a state, and a store. The confusion was generally caused as a result of vaguely discussing Vuex and the capacity of Vue 3&amp;rsquo;s composition API to substitute it for a store-based state management system that could also serve to deliver cache benefits. Who could possibly get lost in that? :)
Cache A cache maintains data for the purpose of reducing performance overhead in accessing the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vue 2 Project Perfect Organization Pattern</title>
      <link>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/vue-2-project-perfect-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 15:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/vue-2-project-perfect-org/</guid>
      <description>Vue 2 is coming to an end. It&amp;rsquo;s only appropriate that the Ultimate Vue Project Organization Pattern™ (UVPOP) would finally be achieved.
There are only a few small ideas, most unoriginal, and it&amp;rsquo;s mostly around organization of modules and their related files and data.
File organization This is heavily inspired by Vue-CLI architecture. The idea is that you should have pages split into folders with page-level components (in this example, titled _page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Loading State</title>
      <link>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/tracking-loading-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 18:46:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>wry-wsac.github.io/posts/tracking-loading-state/</guid>
      <description>WELCOME to my first blog post. Today I want to outline some state management patterns I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with lately, as a jumping off point for further discussions and extreme mental weather systems.
The problem I&amp;rsquo;m trying to address is SPAs have UI components and UX paths that are dependent on asynchronous request states, and the emergent states thereof are driving me insane.
The theoretical example I want you to imagine while working through this article is a registration form that fetches LUT data for some of its fields, in particular for a states drop down/type ahead suggester and a gender select/radio option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
